Guide to the Yakima Valley Grape Producers Records 1934-1973
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Yakima Valley Grape Producers Records
1934-1973
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Cage 368
Yakima Valley Grape Producers
14 containers. 14 linear feet of shelf space. 5700 items.
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial statements, price and purchase information, production data, annual meetings, articles of incorporation and by-laws, and litigation materials of a grape producers' cooperative and its predecessors, the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association and the Valley Grape Growers Association.
The Yakima Valley Grape Producers was established in 1934 as the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association, a non-profit corporation, to sell the products of the members through the Association and its manager.
In 1949 the association was reorganized so that stock could be issued under new state non-profit corporation statutes. At this time all grower equities in the form of certificates of indebtedness in the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association were exchanged for stock certificates in the Valley Grape Growers Association. Each member stockholder was permitted one vote only, regardless of the amount of Class A Common Voting Stock owned. A grower was required to own one share of Class A Common Voting Stock if he annually delivered 15 or more tons of grapes to the Association. While non-growers were permitted to hold stock they were not accorded voting privileges. This transfer of equity took place between 1949 and 1959.
In 1959 the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association was legally dissolved, leaving only the Valley Grape Growers Association, which was renamed the Yakima Valley Grape Producers in 1960.
The records of the Yakima Valley Grape Producers are divided into three series: Correspondence, Internal Organizational Files, and Financial and Fiscal Data.
The Correspondence Series includes alphabetically arranged grower files from 1942 through 1968 containing information on the disposition of stock and holdings of deceased members. General correspondence is arranged alphabetically by year from 1958 through 1972. The material from 1970 through 1972 is arranged alphabetically by subject and general areas. Included in the general correspondence are letters, memoranda, reports, tax returns, employee data, insurance forms, shipping orders, labels and publicity materials.
Internal Organization Files from 1934 through 1970 are arranged alphabetically and include annual meeting information, Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws, meeting minutes, news clippings, and data on litigation proceedings, such as several files on the case of Homer E. Evans vs. the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association, 1953-1958, that include court briefs, correspondence, memoranda and original evidence presented.
Financial and Fiscal Data, 1934-1973, are arranged alphabetically by subject, and chronologically within each subject heading. Accounts receivable, advances to growers, collateral reports, certificates of indebtedness, crop grower ledgers, general ledgers, grower account sheets, inventories, payroll data, trade account sheets, trial balances, and violator lists are included in the Financial and Fiscal Data Series. In 1949 the association was reorganized and renamed, and records for the old corporation (the Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association) as well as for the new corporation (the Valley Grape Growers Association) are both in the same ledgers. This has been noted on the file folder titles. Bound volumes of data have been counted as one item. Undelivered stock, dividend checks, and letters (Folder 390) were randomly sampled and approximately 10 percent of the material was retained.
This collection is open for research use.
The records of the Yakima Valley Grape Producers were donated to the Washington State University Libraries by the organization through General Manager, Robert Thompson in September 1977 (77-57).
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Thompson, Robert. WaPS
Yakima Valley Grape Producers--Archives; Valley Grape Growers Association; Yakima Valley Grape Growers Association
Grapes--Washington (State)--Yakima--Marketing
Agriculture; Washington (State)
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-1972
  - Grower File, 1942-1968
    - Elizabeth Aumiller, 1958; 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - William Achelson, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - L.R. Allen, 1960; 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Emmett and Jack Baird, 1952; 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - F.W. Barlow, 1942-1944; 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bernice Barnes, 1954; 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Walter Barnett, 1953; 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bob Bergamini, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Daniel O. Boyd, 1955; 13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ted Bridges, 1954; 15 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - D.D. Carrier, 1957; 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Edith Cartledge, 1951; 3 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - O.J. Chapman, 1942-1945; 3 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Emile Charvet, 1942-1946; 5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - O. Cheyne, 1960; 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Nels Christiansen, 1942-1947; 5 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Olive Compton, 1955; 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Maud Crawford, 1955; 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Irene Dean, 1953; 12 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alberta Decker, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - George Dixon, 1953; 5 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - W.D. Doran, 1959; 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Elvie M. Eastman, 1953; 10 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - R.B. Elliot, 1952; 2 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - R.A. Folder, 1958; 6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Herbert L. Gant, 1953; 2 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - E.A. Giester (K.P. Lodge) 1949, 1960; 7 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Ernest Grambo, 1951; 1958; 8 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - E.E. Greene, 1960; 7 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - I.W. Hefflinger, 1951; 1960; 10 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Dick Holtkamp, 1955; 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Robert Husseman, 1954; 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - John Jaquish, 1957; 6 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Fred Johnson, 1960; 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Thelma Marie Johnson, 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Alex Kintz, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - J.A. Lane (Dorothy Opperman), 1953; 4 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - J.L. McCord, 1955; 11 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - M.R. and Lois G. McMurray, 1953; 5 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Henry Nagel, 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Raymond Nelson, 1950; 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Costanzo Nicolino, 1957; 1 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jennie May Nostrant, 1956; 2 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Martin Oord, 1960; 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - E.E. Pelz, 1949; 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - O.D. Ray, 1960; 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Lenore Reams, 1954; 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - J.H. Richmond, 1957; 3 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - J.H. Rider, 1964-1968; 5 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - E.R. Rixon, 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - B.R. Root, 1957; 1 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - E.A. Rose, 1958-1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - A.F. Rosenkranz, 1954-1962; 12 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Clarence F. Roy, 1949; 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - George W. Sage, 1960; 6 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Fred Schlien, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Harry Scott, 1960; 3 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - G.C. Seefeldt, 1959-1960; 2 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Selma Shelby, 1952; 1 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Mayme C. Shelton, 1959; 6 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - W.D. Simmons, 1959; 3 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Clyde L. Smith, 1955; 2 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Docia Smith, 1957; 1 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - R.S. Snider, 1959; 2 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Martha Jean Sparrow, 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Claude Stern, 1957; 2 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - E.E. Stump, 1942-1943; 2 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - W.S. Swink, 1954; 1 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - M.A. Taylor, 1953; 2 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - R.B. Tresner, 1958; 1 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Floyd Waterman, 1953; 2 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - William Weber, 1942-1943; 3 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - L. Weichselbaum, 1954; 5 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - J.S. Wertman, 1957-1960; 10 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Frances R. and Emery Wolfe, 1955; 4 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - John Woodson, 1954; 8 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Geneva Work, 1951; 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - William Yarger, 1959-1960; 6 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - J.T. Zimmerman, 1951; 1 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - General--E,F,H,J,M, 1949-1960; 33 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - General Correspondence, 1958-1972
    - 1970
      - Allied Canners & Packers, Inc., 1 (Box 1, Folder 81)
      - American Concord Grape Association, 36 (Box 1, Folder 82)
      - American Can Company, 14 (Box 1, Folder 83)
      - American Farm Lines, Inc., 3 (Box 1, Folder 84)
      - AM Pac Brokerage Co., 18 (Box 1, Folder 85)
      - Barrett Sales Company, 5 (Box 1, Folder 86)
      - Broker Bulletins, 9 (Box 1, Folder 87)
      - Bulletins and Pamphlets, 3 (Box 1, Folder 88)
      - Carr-O'Neill Brokerage, 4 (Box 1, Folder 89)
      - Consolidated Foods Corp., 81 (Box 1, Folder 90)
      - Continental Can Co., 33 (Box 1, Folder 91)
      - Continental Processors, Inc., 13 (Box 1, Folder 92)
      - Wayne Cook, Inc., 1 (Box 1, Folder 93)
      - Desnick Associates, 14 (Box 1, Folder 94)
      - Employment Applications, 33 (Box 1, Folder 95)
      - Exempt Workweeks (Box 1, Folder 96)
      - E. & J. Gallo Winery, 4 (Box 1, Folder 97)
      - Maurey Ginsburg Brokerage, 7 (Box 1, Folder 98)
      - Hall-Roepke, 150 (Box 1, Folder 99)
      - Kenneth Hawkins, 9 (Box 1, Folder 100)
      - Internal Revenue Service, 10 (Box 1, Folder 101)
      - Kelly-Clarke Company, 95 (Box 1, Folder 102)
      - Kerr Brokerage Company, 4 (Box 1, Folder 103)
      - Labels, 60 (Box 1, Folder 104)
      - Manufacturers and Wholesalers Indemnity Exchange, 3 (Box 1, Folder 105)
      - C.K. Murphy Company, 2 (Box 1, Folder 106)
      - National Canners Association, 86 (Box 1, Folder 107)
      - National Canners Association, 50 (Box 1, Folder 108)
      - National Canners Association, 50 (Box 1, Folder 109)
      - National Health Assurance, 16 (Box 1, Folder 110)
      - North Pacific Canners and Packers, Inc., 43 (Box 1, Folder 111)
      - Northwest Chapter of Accountants, 6 (Box 1, Folder 112)
      - Northwest Food Processors Association, 131 (Box 2, Folder 113-114)
      - Nugget Distriubtors, Inc., 26 (Box 2, Folder 115)
      - Red and White Corporation, 1 (Box 2, Folder 116)
      - Alan Robinson and Associates, 4 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - Russell Brokerage Company, 9 (Box 2, Folder 118)
      - Russell-Moss and Associates, 9 (Box 2, Folder 119)
      - Stewart-Tucker, Inc., 17 (Box 2, Folder 120)
      - United Institutional Distributors, 20 (Box 2, Folder 121)
      - W.M. Waters Co., 8 (Box 2, Folder 122)
      - Owens-Illinois, 17 (Box 2, Folder 123)
      - S.A.P.'s, 50 (Box 2, Folder 124)
      - Spokane Bank for Co-operatives, 86 (Box 2, Folder 125)
      - Iiley Thompson, Manager, 30 (Box 2, Folder 126)
      - Vehicle Service Record, 1 (Box 2, Folder 127)
      - Veterans' Administration, 3 (Box 2, Folder 128)
      - Lansing B. Warner, Inc., 30 (Box 2, Folder 129)
      - Weighing and Inspection Dept., 1 (Box 2, Folder 130)
      - State of Washington-Dept. of Labor and Industries, 30 (Box 2, Folder 131)
      - A-Z, 615 (Box 2, Folder 132-139)
    - 1971
      - John Alba vs. Yakima Valley Grape Producers, 3 (Box 2, Folder 140)
      - American Can Company, 5 (Box 2, Folder 141)
      - Am Pac-Jeffrey, 10 (Box 2, Folder 142)
      - Everett Sales Co., 4 (Box 2, Folder 143)
      - Broker Bulletins, 9 (Box 2, Folder 144)
      - Benton Brokerage, 2 (Box 2, Folder 145)
      - Chaney-Waters, Inc., 4 (Box 2, Folder 146)
      - Continental Can Company, 13 (Box 2, Folder 147)
      - Continental Processors, 12 (Box 2, Folder 148)
      - Defense Supply Agency, 7 (Box 2, Folder 149)
      - Desnick Associates, 5 (Box 2, Folder 150)
      - Employee Information & Applications, 55 (Box 2, Folder 151)
      - Exempt Workweeks, 4 (Box 2, Folder 152)
      - J. Hugh Aaron, Attorney, 2 (Box 2, Folder 153)
      - E.& J. Gallo Winery, 33 (Box 2, Folder 154)
      - French-Nelson-Russell, 3 (Box 2, Folder 155)
      - Maury Ginsburg Brokerage, 14 (Box 2, Folder 156)
      - Hall-Roepke Co., 61 (Box 2, Folder 157)
      - Kenneth Hawkins, 1 (Box 2, Folder 158)
      - Internal Revenue, 13 (Box 2, Folder 159)
      - Kelly-Clarke Co., 75 (Box 2, Folder 160)
      - Kerr Brokerage, 3 (Box 2, Folder 161)
      - Labels, 30 (Box 2, Folder 162)
      - Manufacturers & Wholesalers Indemnity Exchange, 4 (Box 2, Folder 163)
      - National Canners Association, 165 (Box 2, Folder 164-166)
      - National Health Association, 15 (Box 2, Folder 167)
      - National Institutional Distributors Assoc. 2 (Box 2, Folder 168)
      - Nelson-Selbert, Inc., 5 (Box 2, Folder 169)
      - North Pacific Canners & Packers, Inc., 5 (Box 3, Folder 170)
      - Northwest Food Processors, 165 (Box 3, Folder 171-172)
      - Nugget Distributors, 14 (Box 3, Folder 173)
      - Alan Robinson & Associates, 8 (Box 3, Folder 174)
      - Russell Moss & Associates, 9 (Box 3, Folder 175)
      - S.A.P.'s, 38 (Box 3, Folder 176)
      - Shipley Jones Pratt Co., 4 (Box 3, Folder 177)
      - Spokane Bank for Cooperatives, 60 (Box 3, Folder 178)
      - State of Washington-Dept. of Labor and Industries, 86 (Box 3, Folder 179)
      - Stewart Tucker, Inc., 14 (Box 3, Folder 180)
      - United Institutional Distributors, 15 (Box 3, Folder 181)
      - Veterans Administration, 3 (Box 3, Folder 182)
      - Lansing B. Warner, 30 (Box 3, Folder 183)
      - Yakima County, 3 (Box 3, Folder 184)
      - Arthur Young & Co., 25 (Box 3, Folder 185)
      - A-M, 324 (Box 3, Folder 186-189)
      - N-Z, 340 (Box 4, Folder 190-194)
    - 1972
      - J. Hugh Aaron, Attorney, 1 (Box 4, Folder 195)
      - Alliance Brokerage & Marketing Corp., 11 (Box 4, Folder 196)
      - Barrett Sales Co., 3 (Box 4, Folder 197)
      - Bulletins and Pamphlets, 11 (Box 4, Folder 198)
      - Carper Sales Co., 13 (Box 4, Folder 199)
      - Carr-O'Neill Brokerage, 2 (Box 4, Folder 200)
      - Continental Can Company, 20 (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - Continental Processors, Inc., 17 (Box 4, Folder 202)
      - Continental Food Sales, Inc., 5 (Box 4, Folder 203)
      - Wayne Cook, Inc., 2 (Box 4, Folder 204)
      - Defense Supply Agency, 10 (Box 4, Folder 205)
      - William O. Dooms Co., 2 (Box 4, Folder 206)
      - Employment Applications, 12 (Box 4, Folder 207)
      - E. & J. Gallo Winery, 9 (Box 4, Folder 208)
      - Maury Ginsburg Brokerage, 9 (Box 4, Folder 209)
      - Stephen Grubb, 4 (Box 4, Folder 210)
      - Hall-Roepke Co., 80 (Box 4, Folder 211)
      - House Rental, 10 (Box 4, Folder 212)
      - Internal Revenue Service, 5 (Box 4, Folder 213)
      - International Brokerage, 4 (Box 4, Folder 214)
      - Kelly-Clarke Co., 44 (Box 4, Folder 215)
      - Labels-Receiving, 38 (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - Marine Insurance, 4 (Box 4, Folder 217)
      - Manufacturers & Wholesalers Indemnity Exchange, 7 (Box 4, Folder 218)
      - Moss, Adams & Co., 18 (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - National Canners Assoc., 108 (Box 4, Folder 220-221)
      - National Institutional Distributors Ass., 1 (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - Nelson Selberg, Inc., 13 (Box 4, Folder 223)
      - Northwest Food Processors, 75 (Box 4, Folder 224-225)
      - Nugget Distributors, Inc., 25 (Box 4, Folder 226)
      - Occupational Safety and Health Admin., 17 (Box 4, Folder 227)
      - Alan Robinson & Associates, 10 (Box 4, Folder 228)
      - Russell-Moss & Associates, 15 (Box 5, Folder 229)
      - J.B. Ruth & Co., 6 (Box 5, Folder 230)
      - Shipley Jones Pratt Co., 5 (Box 5, Folder 231)
      - Spokane Bank for Cooperatives, 45 (Box 5, Folder 232)
      - State of Washington-Dept. of Labor and Industries, 87 (Box 5, Folder 233)
      - Stewart Tucker Company, 6 (Box 5, Folder 234)
      - United Institutional Distributors Corp., 9 (Box 5, Folder 235)
      - United States Department of Agriculture, 19 (Box 5, Folder 236)
      - Federal Unemployment Form 940, 3 (Box 5, Folder 237)
      - Veterans Administration, 2 (Box 5, Folder 238)
      - Lansing B. Warner, Inc., 21 (Box 5, Folder 239)
      - Washington Agricultural Marketing Assoc., 4 (Box 5, Folder 240)
      - Washington State Grape Society, 2 (Box 5, Folder 241)
      - Western Family Foods, Inc., 10 (Box 5, Folder 242)
      - Yakima County, 3 (Box 5, Folder 243)
      - Arthur Young & Co., 5 (Box 5, Folder 244)
      - A-Z, 456 (Box 5, Folder 245-251)
    - 1966-1969, 18 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - E. & J. Gallo, 1969; 23 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1958-1960; 1 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Arthur Young & Co., 1967-1970; 27 (Box 5, Folder 255)
- Series 2: Internal Organizational Files, 1934-1970
  - Annual Meetings, 1949-1969 (Box 5, Folder 256-262)
  - Articles of Incorporation,By-Laws, 1934-1965; 17 (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1958-1970; 23 (Box 6, Folder 264-265)
  - Bids, 1968-1970; 6 (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Homer E. Evans vs. Yakima Valley Grape Growers, 1953-1958
    - Briefs, 1957-1958; 3 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Correspondence and Court Documents, 1953-1958; 35 (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Exhibits and Evidence, 1953-1958; 22 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Exhibits and Evidence, 1953-1958; 27 (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - General Information, 1953-1958; 1 (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - Newspaper Clippings--Grape Industry, 1955-1962; 2 (Box 6, Folder 272-273)
  - Rathke vs. Yakima Valley Grape Growers, undated; 1 (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - Yakima Valley Grape Growers vs. W.R.Copeland, 1950; 1 (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - Yakima Valley Grape Growers vs. Fred Reihs,et.al., 1949; 1 (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Yakima Valley Grape Growers vs. Welch Grape Juice, 1947-1950; 1 (Box 6, Folder 277)
- Series 3: Financial and Fiscal Data, 1934-1973
  - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1953-1954; 1 (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - Advances to Growers, 1959-1960; 2 (Box 6, Folder 279-280)
  - Audit Reports, 5 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Bulletin to Growers, Equities, 1948-1951; 1 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Certificates of Indebtedness, 1942-1947; 17 (Box 7, Folder 283-285)
  - Contracts, Notes Payable, 1944-1958; 1 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Contract List, 1951; 1 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Collateral Reports, 1962-1967; 22 (Box 7, Folder 288-292)
  - Crop Grower Ledgers, 1967-1973
    - 1967-1971, 4 (Box 7, Folder 293-296)
    - 1971-1973, 2 (Box 8, Folder 297-298)
  - Crop Harvest Statements, 1968-1969; 2 (Box 8, Folder 299-300)
  - Distribution Prior Pool Equities, 1948-1951; 1 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - General Ledgers, 1948-1970
    - 1948-1953, 5 (Box 8, Folder 302-306)
    - 1953-1970, 11 (Box 9, Folder 307-317)
  - Grower Account Sheets, 1946-1966
    - 1946-1947, 2 (Box 9, Folder 318-319)
    - 1947-1952, 10 (Box 10, Folder 320-330)
    - (1953-1955 includes both VGGA & YVGGA), 1952-1962; 13 (Box 11, Folder 331-343)
    - 1962-1966, 6 (Box 12, Folder 344-349)
  - Growers' Delivery Records, 1946-1954; 1 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - Employee Withholding Statements, 1955-1960; 7 (Box 12, Folder 351-352)
  - Inventories, 1965-1967; 5 (Box 12, Folder 353-354)
  - Payroll, 1957-1967
    - 1957-1960, 3 (Box 12, Folder 355-357)
    - 1959-1967, 9 (Box 13, Folder 358-366)
  - Report of Examination, 1948-1967; 6 (Box 13, Folder 367)
  - Revolving Finance Fund Certificates, 1955-1956; 1 (Box 13, Folder 368)
  - Stock Transfer, A-B, 1955; 4 (Box 13, Folder 369)
  - Sugar Solids and Payments, 1961-1966; 2 (Box 13, Folder 370-371)
  - Tax Payments & Information, 1955-1959; 1 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - Trade Accounts, 1948-1953; 5 (Box 13, Folder 373-377)
  - Trademark Copyright, 1956-1959; 1 (Box 13, Folder 378)
  - Transfer of Equity Record-YVGGA to VGGA, 1942-1946
    - Book 1, 1 (Box 13, Folder 379)
    - Book 2, 1 (Box 14, Folder 380)
  - Trial Balances, 1960-1967; 41 (Box 14, Folder 381-387)
  - Undelivering Contracted Growers, 1947-1950; 1 (Box 14, Folder 388)
  - Undelivered Stock, 1943-1947; 3 (Box 14, Folder 389)
  - Undelivered Stock, Dividend Checks, Letters, 1952-1959; 20 (Box 14, Folder 390)
  - Violators
    - B List, 1949-1950; 17 (Box 14, Folder 391)
    - Class D., 1948; 1 (Box 14, Folder 392)
    - Pool Balances, 1948-1951; 1 (Box 14, Folder 393)
    - Unclassified, 1945-1951; 27 (Box 14, Folder 394)